<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cs3216 on Goh Wei Wen</title>
    <link>https://goweiwen.github.io/tags/cs3216/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cs3216 on Goh Wei Wen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 23:02:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://goweiwen.github.io/tags/cs3216/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2 Of CS3216</title>
      <link>https://goweiwen.github.io/blog/week-2-of-cs3216/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 23:02:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goweiwen.github.io/blog/week-2-of-cs3216/</guid>
      <description>Week 2 ends with two deliverables due on the midnight of Friday.
My team&#39;s Orbital presentation happened earlier this week. One of the advisors for the Orbital project took CS3216 during his second year. He mentioned that in retrospect, taking it in year three, after CS3217, would be a better choice. That scared me, but I&#39;m confident I&#39;ll be able to overcome any obstacles CS3216 throws.
At the Orbital presentation, I bumped into another pair from this year&#39;s intake, who told me that they had dropped this module.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1 Of CS3216</title>
      <link>https://goweiwen.github.io/blog/week-1-of-cs3216/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 22:17:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goweiwen.github.io/blog/week-1-of-cs3216/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Colin started our first lecture flying a drone in class. I guess that&#39;s one way to tell students that CS3216 isn&#39;t your normal module.
Coming in as a year 2 student, I didn&#39;t expect to see anyone I recognize in class. When I stepped into the room, however, I was greeted by Kush, my block mate from Raffles Hall. Seeing a familiar face definitely eased my first day of class anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I hope to learn in CS3216</title>
      <link>https://goweiwen.github.io/blog/what-i-hope-to-learn-in-cs2316/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 22:42:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goweiwen.github.io/blog/what-i-hope-to-learn-in-cs2316/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CS3216 is famed for enrolling motivated and hardworking students. I believe that by being surrounded by such passionate people, I will be able to push past my comfort zone and improve myself beyond my own limits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few things I hope to learn in this module:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>